Mind over matter
The Brain is a horror, science fiction film directed by Ed Hunt.
Blake runs a TV show called "Independent Thinkers", which is sort
of a Scientology-like self-help/religion program.
But he's not making his audience think any more independently - with the help of an alien
organism he calls The Brain, he's using brainwashing and mind control.
The only thing that stands between them and world domination is a brilliant
but troubled high school student with a penchant for pranks...
Jim Majelewski, played by Tom Bresnahan.
Janet, played by Cynthia Preston.
Dr. Anthony Blakely, played by David Gale.
Verna, played by George Buza.
Willie, played by Bret Pearson.
Vivian, played by Christine Kossak.
The Brain is a 1988 Canadian science fiction horror film depicting a giant
brain-like alien that mentally enslaves a town's residents.
The film explores themes of high school,
hallucination, car crash, alien, murder.
The tone is dark and thought_provoking.